Contact

- NG6 9JE , Nottingham
- 07913686584
- amiragucher@gmail.co m
- https://www.linkedin.co m/in/amira-gucher-black man-
- https://github.com/amir agucher

Skills

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

Tailwind

Next Js

React

Postgress

Jest

Node

Postman

Typescript

Heroku

Vercel

Auth0

Figma

Miro

Cypress

Express



Personal Profile

Prior to studying at the School of Code my studies evolved around Art and Design, and then Psychology. During the bootcamp I found a true passion for coding which has only grown over time. I have experience of working with people from all walks of life and have gained the ability to work within a team and in an agile framework. Through the School of Code, I have developed both leadership and team work skills and the ability to problem solve and come up with solutions. I am committed, hard working, pro-active and passionate and am ready to contribute to a company successes.

• Recent Experience

School Of Code Graduate May 2022 - August 2022

Recently graduated from the School Of Code bootcamp. During the bootcamp I was introduced to a wide range of programming utilities and languages which has given me the confidence and understanding of a wide variety of areas within tech. I have gained the ability to work within an agile framework and have experience working within a tight time schedule and under pressure.

- Training in agile development
- Weekly Hackathons and presentations
- Trained in a range of technologies (as shown in skills section)
- Experience with leadership and project management
- Experience with working within a team successfully
- Advanced design skills with Figma and Miro

Work History

2020-12 - **Volunteer**

2021-12

Gig Buddies For Good Mental Health

- My role included writing blogs about mental health at university
- I also worked with an individual with mental health challenges
- I would meet up with my gig buddy once a month and communicate with them regularly.

2018-07 - **Personal Carer**

2021-06

Brighton, East Sussex

- I cared for a teenage girl with autism once a week
- This role included going out for walks anddoing activities such as drawing and crafts.

2020-04 - Warehouse Assistant

2020-08

Old Town Trader

 My role involved talking to customers, administration, processing and shipping orders.

2019-05 - Sales Assistant, Artist

2020-01

Anon

- This role involved opening and closing the shop, serving customers, managing the shopdisplay and cashing up at the end of the day
- I ran the shop on my own.

2018-07 - Sales Assistant

2019-08

Jack Wills

- My role included interacting with customers as well as cleaning the shop and making sure all the stock is out
- I would occasionally work in the stock room dealing with deliveries and stock taking.

2019-01 - Volunteer at Jatan Sansthan NGO

2019-04

India

International Citizenship Service - ICS

 I volunteered in India for three months and worked on three projects including women's health, facilitating youth groups and providing teaching support at a nursery.

Education

| 2022-04 - 2022-08 | Bootcamp: Software Developer School Of Code - Online |
|----------------------|--|
| 20190 - 2021-07 | University of Brighton I have spent the past two years studying Psychology and Counselling. I have deferred my third year so that I can gain work experienceand will be completing it at a later date. |
| 2018-09 - 2019-06 | Brighton Metropolitan College Psychology Access to Higher Education course |
| 2015-09 - 2017-06 | BTEC Sussex Downs College Art and Design |
| 2008-09 - 2015-01 | Moira House School including English and Maths. |

Declaration

Full, clean driving license
This CV may be kept on file and distributed for employment purposes